You know what else is not stealing?
Putting an extra bike lock on a
stranger's bike.
It is great to be here. I uh
started jogging.
Mentioned that to a friend of mine who
does it a lot and he was like, "Oh, you
need to shave your legs so you go
faster."
>> [laughter]
>> This guy has a beard.
But I was like, "No, I don't need to
you know, I'm fine with my
resistance workout."
>> [laughter]
>> But he was persistent and he was like,
"No, man, listen, I've been riding my
bike to work for years and I started
shaving my legs every day, cut 2 minutes
off the commute."
It's like, "But how long does it take
you to shave?"
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, you can shave your legs faster if
your arms are shaved.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> Read this article online that had all of
these amazing facts about the human body
and one of them said that the average
human being skin our skin is so
sensitive we can feel the weight of a
bee's wing.
That's 1/10,000
of an ounce. If that's true, I'm below
I've gone an entire day without
realizing I had another pair of my
underwear in my pant leg.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> I was I was looking at a map of the
United States and I know that we were
colonized from east to west.
Right to left. But it looks like it was
the other way around. It looks like the
founding fathers approached some guy and
they had like an outline of the future
country on a piece of paper and they
gave him that and a pen and said,
"Listen, we need you to divide this into
50 sections. Start on the left side."
And he was like, "Oh, yeah, there is
plenty of room.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> If you don't get that, you shouldn't be
allowed to vote.
>> [laughter]
>> I live in uh Burbank, California.
I have a landline telephone, came with
the tiny house that I rent. And uh
second of my neighbor in our front
yards, this guy's nosy.
Some of us have that neighbor. He very
casually threw this into the
conversation. He was like, "Hey Kellen,
the other day I picked up part of a
conversation from your cordless phone
through my baby monitor."
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, that's that's a real thing. I
didn't know. I also didn't know how to
respond.
He's just smiling like a weirdo.
>> [laughter]
>> So, I said, "Actually, I don't have a
cordless phone.
But occasionally, I do stand in your
baby's room and talk to him."
>> [applause]
>> Probably what that was. Anything else?
No? Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I'm not a creep. I have two kids. I
want to have three. That's the perfect
number, right? You can finally be on the
Family Feud.
>> [laughter]
>> But also, with three kids, a mom and a
dad, that's how many people comfortably
fit in a log at Disneyland.
>> [laughter]
>> Right? You have a fourth child, you have
to buy another picture.
>> [laughter]
>> It's like 30 bucks just for a snapshot
of your toddler straddling some Russian
couple.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't want that on my mantle.
>> You ever have this happen where you're
at home and your phone's about to die,
so you plug it in while you're talking?
Yeah.
Just me and her. The rest of you don't
have to.
>> [laughter]
>> Just ignore this next joke.
>> I do that. I always forget that the cord
is only 11 in long.
So for the next half hour I end up
kneeling next to a dresser.
>> [laughter]
>> I just want to know who designed that
cord. I imagine a couple of scientists
in the Verizon laboratory and one of
them's like, "Hey, why don't we make it
long enough so they can sit on the
couch?"
And his supervisor's like, "That's
ridiculous.
>> [laughter]
>> So they didn't do it before bedtime,
it's their fault.
Don't worry though, I'm making this
other cord stretches out to 9 or 10 ft
and they could only use it in their
cars."
>> [laughter]
>> The most selfish thing that a human
being can do is leave an empty shopping
cart in a parking space.
Yeah, if you've done that shame on you.
You're telling me you can meander 2 and
1/2 miles inside Costco and the moment
you get to your vehicle you're like,
"Not another step."
>> [laughter]
>> Timed out my physical endurance down to
this moment.
>> [laughter]
>> Can't push it 20 ft, help everyone else
out. That's why I don't even care. You
guys can try this too. Uh every time I'm
inside a grocery store I take someone
else's cart.
>> [laughter]
>> Do it. Full of food, take it. It is so
much faster.
>> [laughter]
>> And you get to try new things.
>> Do it. It's not wrong. Tell me how
that's wrong.
>> [laughter]
>> It's not stealing.
>> [clears throat]
>> What could they possibly even say to
you? Excuse me, I gathered that.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
[laughter]
>> You just say thanks and you can
regather. You know the route.
>> [laughter]
>> That's how I found out that I like
hummus.
You know what else is not stealing?
Putting an extra bike lock on a
stranger's bike.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> It's insane that bike locks are legal,
that they're just available to the
public. Do you have any idea the amount
of power that you wield
with your imagination and a bike lock?
There's [laughter] so many things. Like
you could just walk past a Baskin
Robbins and be like, "You're closed."
>> [laughter]
>> It is so arbitrary what we need
permission to buy and what we don't. You
have to show photo ID in a hobby shop to
buy paint. Yet, all of us here are just
one Amazon click away from buying orange
cones and making traffic go wherever we
want.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't like buying milk. All right,
they don't they'll sell any other
product that way. You grab a bag of
marshmallows off the shelf, all the
other marshmallows don't come at you.
>> [laughter]
>> Milk, the heaviest item in the store,
they sell on a ramp that's aimed at your
face. [laughter]
I mean, pull one gallon off, seven
others slam forward. It's 2%, you wanted
nonfat, but now you can't put it back.
>> [laughter]
>> I discovered though, you push those
other milks hard enough, they disappear.
>> [laughter]
>> In the healthy grocery stores, I I never
buy anything from that aisle of barrels.
All right, I just don't like how
accessible it is to like bare hands
or the air.
>> [laughter]
>> Here's what I do though, I go up to the
most expensive granola and I scoop it
into the cheapest one.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm the Robin Hood of Whole Foods.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> Oh, you didn't clap long enough for me
to take a drink.
So, what did you guys do for Valentine's
Day?
Sushi? All right, that's cool. Woohoo,
food poisoning. What else?
>> [laughter]
>> What's that?
You studied?
It's like the saddest thing you could
say.
>> [laughter]
>> Now, no one else is going to answer cuz
they're going to
feel bad that they had plans.
Anything?
>> A date with my kids.
A day with your kids?
>> divorce.
Wow.
Let's dig into this.
She's like, where are the brakes to this
joke? Oh, here.
>> [laughter]
>> No, we could say anything.
>> This boy, I did something happy. I'm
sorry.
It's just a total like genre twist to
this whole show.
>> [laughter]
>> Let us discuss this.
>> Celebrate divorce.
>> [laughter]
>> Notice how no one clapped.
>> It's a great segue into what I had
prepared.
>> [laughter]
>> Usually [laughter] it's like
went to a restaurant, my wife wrote my
wife a song, and then I'm like, oh, and
here's what I did. And you're like, no,
stop everything.
>> [laughter]
>> Next holiday.
I got robbed last Christmas. Do
something with that.
>> [applause]
[applause]
>> It's a comedy
course.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, here's what I did.
>> I understand now this isn't going to be
for everyone.
>> [laughter]
>> I think I'll just do the talking from
now on.
The rest of my set is just me talking
about it, not even doing jokes.
>> [laughter]
>> Here we go.
I ordered my wife one of those edible
arrangements fruit bouquets.
You know what I'm talking about? It's
cool. It's a It's a nice thing. Well, I
want to get in on that business model.
Cuz I paid $70 and I didn't even think
twice about it. I was like, "Oh, that
sounds right." It's not right.
Their profit margin is probably amazing.
It's fruit. What's their overhead?
Like a product should cost as much as
the materials plus the skill required to
assemble them, right? For $70, I could
buy a printer.
And that makes sense. I don't know how
to make a printer.
>> [laughter]
>> Fruit bouquet on the other hand,
after quick analysis, pretty easy to
reverse engineer that thing.
There was maybe like collectively half a
pineapple cut into heart shapes on
sticks for what I gave my wife. $70. My
wife loves fruit. Next year, 70 bucks,
I'm just going to give her like 40
pineapples.
>> [laughter]
>> I want to be rich. I want to be so
wealthy
so that like anytime I wanted it, I
could just buy all the tickets to a
Maroon 5 concert and go by myself.
>> [laughter]
>> And boo after every
song.
>> [applause]
>> I would
I would sit front and center so when
they came out they'd be like, "Oh, I
guess there was a mistake." And I'd be
like, "No, this is happening."
>> [laughter]
>> This is a sold-out show, Adam.
>> Hey, stage dive.
>> [laughter]
>> Let's make this Maroon 4.
[laughter]
>> This is Utah. How many of you guys drove
to the border to get lottery tickets
when that Powerball went over a billion?
Anyone here? Yeah, a couple of you. I
bought a ticket. Never bought a lottery
ticket in my life. And it wasn't just
me. There were thousands of first-time
lottery ticket buyers. It was on the
news, right? People were lined up for
hours. Which is crazy in retrospect
because that means that even when that
jackpot was at 975 million, I was like,
"Nah."
>> [laughter]
>> What even is that after taxes, right?
>> It's crazier than that though are the
odds to the Powerball. The odds are 1 in
300 million.
1 in 300 million. To paint a picture of
that, in the entire Western Hemisphere
from Canada down to Chile, there are 900
million people. That averages out to
about 300 million households. So, what
if this is how the game were played? You
walk in to buy your ticket, there's a
man in a suit to explain the game to
you. Hey, welcome to the Powerball.
Here's how it goes. We've placed a
billion dollars in a box. Now, we've
hidden this box
in a random bedroom somewhere upon the
American continent.
>> [laughter]
>> Now, here's the fun part. You give us
$2, you get one shot to guess that
address.
>> [laughter]
>> My favorite game growing up was
Battleship. You guys remember that?
Loved it uh till I figured out they
could have just called it number letter.
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz there is no wartime strategy.
And well, it's bingo with toys on it.
Can you imagine if that ship battle
scenario ever actually happened?
A general briefing his men, he's like,
"All right, listen up. Here's the
situation.
There are five enemy ships out there
exactly like our five ships.
>> [laughter]
>> We have no idea where they are. Uh but
we do have good intel that they're not
moving.
>> [laughter]
>> Or diagonal.
>> So, when you fire at them, I just just
guess. Um
I'll fire one, stop, let them fire one
back.
>> [laughter]
>> It's a war, we take turns.
Oh, and every time after we fly our
missile, we need to ask him how it went.
>> [laughter]
>> Played baseball growing up. Did you know
that the dimensions to a baseball field
are just whatever?
It's completely true. Every Major League
baseball field is different. The
infield's always the same.
90 ft to each base, but the outfield
fence, they just make it up.
This is 100% true. To hit a home run in
Fenway Park, Boston Red Sox have got to
hit that ball 302 ft.
Houston Astros, on the other hand,
Minute Maid Park, they have to hit the
ball 436
ft.
That's a 45% difference.
And no one ever talks about it. Like
maybe there's a reason why the Red Sox
have been to 13 World Series.
>> [laughter]
>> And the Astros are swept in one.
>> It's like, "Hey guys, there's no rule.
Move in your fence.
Make it easier on yourselves."
>> [laughter]
>> A 45% difference. Can you imagine if any
other sport just decided to start doing
that, there'd be an uproar, right?
You see that excited NBA coach, "Hey,
great news, guys. We're playing in
Chicago this week. The rims there are
only 5 and 1/2 ft tall."
>> [laughter]
>> So, a a Tesla can park itself, which is
fancy. However, my Nissan has this
feature where it'll beep
loudly to let me know if my groceries
haven't buckled their seatbelt.
And I am so excited for self-driving
cars. Anyone else? I am very Not
Few people, right? Other people are
afraid. Don't be. It's going to be
great.
Don't be scared. Ask yourself this. Have
you ever walked into a grocery store and
had those doors just like pinch you?
Never, right?
>> [laughter]
>> So,
imagine that automation technology
>> [laughter]
>> improved by a factor of a million.
That's what they're putting on cars.
It's going to be okay.
You still don't believe me?
Would you rather there be like two dudes
inside every grocery store just manually
sliding those doors
as your family walks in, right?
One of the guys is texting, the other is
high. That's what you want?
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz when you're driving, that's what's
happening around you constantly.
It's usually older people, like much
older people, who are skeptical of the
idea of having a computer drive their
car. Here's what I want to say. If
you're like 70, 75 plus, and you're
afraid of a computer driving your car,
here's what I want you to do. Go to
WebMD
where you can list your symptoms. Just
go ahead and put in like every part of
your body that aches or is immobile.
Add the painkillers that maybe you take
every day. I think you might find that
the computer's skeptical of you driving
a car.
>> [laughter]
>> Last time that my car was dirty, my
friend did the obvious thing, scrawled
out wash me on the back window. So, I
went up to the side of his car with a
key and wrote touch me up.
>> [cheering and laughter]
>> I had to renew my license recently in
California. Every 10 years or so you
have to make the trip to the DMV
and retake the picture, right? I always
hate it, right? Then 3 years ago it goes
by and I wish I looked that good.
>> [laughter]
>> But how about that Costco ID membership
picture, right? No amount of time ever
goes by that I wish I looked like that
walking dead version of my face.
>> [laughter]
>> Costco's a billion-dollar industry. They
can only afford a camera with like seven
pixels.
That's the only thing that doesn't come
in bulk.
>> [laughter]
>> Like they have better cameras they sell
in the store. They could just grab one,
write it off, and use it forever. But
they don't. You know why? You know no
one ever looks at that picture. It
doesn't matter.
I walk in and I flash them my library
card. They don't care.
>> [laughter]
>> It's a dumb idea in the first place.
What are they afraid someone's going to
sneak in and buy stuff?
I was mowing my lawn recently. I noticed
every lawn mower has a throttle on it,
but the speeds aren't labeled with the
words high or low. Does anybody know
what it has instead?
Turtle and a rabbit.
That guy was ready.
That [laughter] was
That was very quick. That guy's been
going to comedy shows every weekend for
like 10 years.
>> [laughter]
>> He's like, "Finally, they asked the lawn
mower question."
Just walks out.
But it's true. There's a turtle and a
rabbit, which is insane cuz that means
that at the lawnmower factory they're
like, "Yeah, we don't care if they can
read."
As long as they know their fables.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> I'm disappointed with the lack of
originality when it comes to naming high
school football teams, especially when
it comes to animals. There are a
trillion species on this planet, only
nine are used for all sports. I can
prove it right now. Go ahead and clap if
your high school football team was the
Eagles.
We have some Eagles here. All right. How
about Bears? WHAT ABOUT BEARS?
WOW.
LIKE I THINK HIGH SCHOOL MATTERED. All
right.
>> [laughter]
>> How about Lions? Do we have any Lions
here?
>> [applause]
>> Just a couple of cowardly lions in the
back.
How about Wildcats? Do we have any of
those? Yeah.
That's not even a thing.
>> [laughter]
>> It's a lazy meeting.
What are you going to be? I don't know,
some sort of wildcat. Yep, that's it.
Meeting adjourned.
>> [laughter]
>> I always do like to ask if anybody here
come from a high school that had a
unique team name. So, nothing that's
ever been used in like professional
sports, NFL, NBA, baseball. Just go
ahead and yeah, just don't tell it to
me, just cheer.
>> [laughter]
>> What was that? What was that? The
Buckaroos?
>> [laughter]
>> Everyone cheering just sounds like a
condescending dad. There you go,
Buckaroo.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> Even when you win it can't feel good.
Good job, Buckaroo.
>> [laughter]
>> What else What else do we have over
here? Darts.
What's that? The scars? Darts.
Darts. Oh, the darts.
>> [laughter]
>> She did a little The darts.
Oh, okay, the pointy ones. All right.
>> [laughter]
>> I
thought you meant the car.
>> [laughter]
>> That'd be weirder. The darts.
>> Did your parents Okay, just a second.
We're still [laughter]
We're still talking about darts.
What What city are you from or state?
What's that? Kaysville, Utah. Kaysville,
Utah? Okay. All right.
Is that like a thing there?
>> [laughter]
>> That's number one on Trip Advisor for
Kaysville.
Dude, they have the best darts in
Kaysville. Are you saying that?
No, no, the pointy ones.
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> What else do we have?
What's that? Beat digger. Beat digger.
That came from the cheap seats in the
balcony, of course.
>> That's how we earned our way here.
Where are you from that you dig beets?
>> [laughter]
>> What's that?
Jordan High School? All right.
That's that's here, right?
This this is going all over the world,
so people aren't going to know.
It's like Jordan, so it's just some guy.
>> [laughter]
>> Jordan likes beets. I don't know.
Over here, somebody raise your hand
politely. What was yours?
The russets?
Okay.
Someone other guy just yelled his out.
He's like, "That's not interesting.
Listen to mine."
>> [laughter]
>> What's Okay. All right, russets are
potatoes. Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Getting heckled by Wikipedia.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> Usually when I get heckled, someone's
like, "Get off the stage." But you guys
are like, "Here's some useful
information."
>> [laughter]
[cheering]
>> All right, potatoes.
>> [laughter]
>> What else? What else do we have?
The caveman? All right, cool. Where are
you Where are you from?
American Fork? All right, I don't know a
thing about that.
Caveman, what else?
The Dons?
Spanish Fork?
>> [laughter]
>> Feel like everyone here knows something
but me.
I don't understand all these utensil
cities.
>> [laughter]
>> The criminals.
>> You from Spanish Fork, too?
>> [applause]
>> I'm just guessing. I'm glad it made
sense to you guys.
Anyone else not from here?
>> [laughter]
>> Is there a couple What's that?
Patriots. Cool. You weren't listening to
my question. All right.
This
>> [laughter]
>> I'm Chicago Fork right there.
The syrup makers. The syrup makers?
The rest of you quiet down for a second.
>> [laughter]
>> He is trying to help me out. That what
it
I'm from Georgia, so He's from Georgia,
of course. I love the syrup from
Georgia.
So matter-of-fact.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought you were going to be like,
"Obviously, I'm from Canada." But it was
like, "No, I'm
Georgia." [laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> She's like, "Russets, yeah. Yeah."
I'm from Saudi Arabia.
Obviously.
>> [laughter]
>> So, the shirt makers? Yeah, shirt
makers. Okay. What was So, what was your
mascot? Just like a really bored guy?
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
[applause]
>> If I could name my high school team,
it'd be the Chameleons. Wouldn't that be
great?
Every game, you just dress up like the
other team.
They have acupuncture for pets. I would
love to go to a pet acupuncturist with a
porcupine.
Just for that walk back through the
waiting room. Like, I don't know what
they did to my cat.
>> [laughter]
>> It's the last time I use a Groupon.
>> My favorite animal is a penguin. I just
I just feel bad for them. Penguins are
the reason why I don't completely
believe in the theory of evolution.
>> [laughter]
>> I guess evolution says that an animal
either die off or adapt comfortably to
its environment.
I just don't think they belong in
Antarctica. They seem cold.
>> [laughter]
>> Like, go to the LA Zoo. They don't keep
them in a freezer. They're on cement and
they're fine.
>> [laughter]
>> Every other animal in the South Pole has
at least 15 in of blubber or fur to keep
it warm. You ever seen a penguin walk?
They walk the same way you would if you
were wearing cold wet pants.
This is completely true. Every year in
Antarctica, penguins walk 80 miles round
trip for food, if you believe Morgan
Freeman.
>> [laughter]
>> Here's where evolution gets shady. If
these poor animals have been walking 80
miles every year for the past 10 million
years, why don't they have knees yet?
>> [laughter]
>> Their wings haven't worked out for some
reason.
Can they at least get some bendy legs?
>> [laughter]
>> You ever see them do that thing where
they slide on their bellies into the
ocean? They never mean to do that.
They just trip and they're like, "Well,
I can't get up."
Guess I'll learn how to swim, too. I'm a
bird.
My buddy was telling me about that
movie, The Revenant. I haven't seen it.
I might. I just didn't agree with his
reason
for encouraging me to watch the film.
He's like, "You got to see it. Leonardo
DiCaprio finally won the Oscar for that
film. And it's a good thing he won the
Oscar cuz he worked so hard on that
movie."
And that's where I disagree.
My friend said, "It's a good thing he
won that Oscar because he worked so hard
on that movie. They shot it for 9 months
in the blistering cold of Canada. He
walked through those rivers himself. He
lost 35 lb during those 9 months. Isn't
that amazing?" And I said, "If you think
that's amazing,
you severely underestimate what I would
do for $20 million.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Like there's not a person in this room
who wouldn't do everything that he did
for that amount of money. Right? If he
acted well, give him the Oscar for that,
but not just because he worked for
almost a year.
>> [laughter]
>> $20 million. He lost 35 lb. I would get
down to 35 lb.
>> [laughter]
>> All right. My la- my last few jokes
here.
I
They never got what they deserved.
And I think it's because comedy's all
about timing, and my timing is too good.
So, I have Siri read them, and it makes
them a lot better cuz she's the worst.
>> [laughter]
[clears throat]
>> Testing. Testing. Testing.
Is that good?
All right. That was the first one.
>> [laughter]
>> It's always a pleasant surprise when you
find an unexpected $10 in the jacket
pocket of a stranger.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> This is something I have never heard a
wealthy person say. It all started when
I read Rich Dad, Poor Dad.
>> [laughter]
[cheering]
[applause]
[laughter]
>> The person who said to drink eight to 10
cups of water a day for your health
forgot that it also makes you enter five
to seven public restrooms a day.
>> [applause]
>> Best Buy is a great place to try out
stuff that you can then buy cheaper on
Amazon.
>> [applause]
>> Maybe flies would live longer than 24
hours if they didn't eat poo.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Ever since California voted against
stores giving out free plastic bags, I
have collected so many shopping baskets
from Target.
>> [applause]
>> Google is turning 18 years old this
year. I cannot believe it was just 19
years ago that I never researched
anything ever.
>> [laughter]
>> It's my greatest fear that the world
will be destroyed and the only remaining
humans will be me and all those people
who use the internet at the library.
>> [applause]
[laughter]
>> The secret to looking younger is to tell
people you are older.
>> [laughter]
>> If you want to feel like Superman, take
a paintball gun to a laser tag arena.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, you guys have been great. I'm
going to leave you with this one.
TVs are getting thinner, but people are
getting fatter, so everyone is still the
same distance from the screen.
>> [cheering]
>> Thank you guys very much.
>> [music]